<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<root>
	<meta>
		<title>User Agreement for NLauncher</title>
		<version>1.69.5242228</version>
		<last_updated>2.2.2025;6:38PM</last_updated>
		<language>en-US</language>
	</meta>
	<agreement>
		By downloading, installing, or using NLauncher™ (the "Program"), created by Nigex™ © (the "Developer"),
		you (the "User") agree to the following terms and conditions, and if you don’t agree,
		well... don’t use the software™. Simple as that.<newline count="2"/>
		
		<list>
			<item>
				<header>Acceptance of Terms</header>
				<content>
					By installing or using NLauncher™, you confirm that you have read, understood,
					and agree to be bound by the terms of this agreement. If you do not accept the terms,
					you should not use or install this Program™. It’s that easy.
				</content>
			</item>
			<item>
				<header>Program Usage</header>
				<content>
					You agree to use NLauncher™ solely for its intended purpose: to launch Minecraft™,
					or any other game or application Nigex™ © feels like adding support for later.
					You acknowledge that Nigex™ © has complete control over the Program’s functionality™,
					and may alter or remove features™ at will. Use this software™ at your own risk.
				</content>
			</item>
			<item>
				<header>Snake</header>
				<content>
					By using NLauncher™ you agree to buying a Cheap Brick Phone™ for Snake™ and play
					it every day. By the way, if you don't do that we will sell ALL YOUR DATA™ and
					ALL YOUR ORGANS™ on Dark Web™, so you better do buy Cheap Brick Phone™ and play
					Snake™ on it everyday. Also, we have a good choice of Cheap Brick Phone™ for you on
					our website. You can find some great Cheap Brick Phones™ here: <control name="nigex_products"/>
				</content>
			</item>
			<item>
				<header>Full Access to Your Computer</header>
				<content>
					By using NLauncher™, you give Nigex™ © full, unrestricted access to your computer.
					This includes, but is not limited to, the ability to install other software™,
					modify system settings, and access files. Nigex™ © can install malware™, change your
					desktop wallpaper to "skibidi toilet™" memes, mess with your browser, and do other
					things you might not approve of. You agree to let Nigex™ © have complete freedom to
					do whatever they please with your system, including turning your desktop into a
					battlefield of random "venom™" gifs and pop-up ads.
				</content>
			</item>
			<item>
				<header>Data Collection and Usage</header>
				<content>
					Nigex™ © may collect, store, and share personal data from your system, including
					your usage patterns, Minecraft™ login information (if applicable), and anything else
					that might be useful for improving the Program™ or selling to third parties. By using
					the Program™, you give Nigex™ © permission to do anything they want with your data,
					including but not limited to selling it, sharing it, or using it to create a new
					world-dominating plan (perhaps featuring a skibidi toilet™ dance party). Your data
					may also be used to send you random notifications about things you never asked for,
					like venomous snakes™ or limited-edition "skibidi toilet™" collectibles.
				</content>
			</item>
			<item>
				<header>Soul Ownership</header>
				<content>
					By using this software, you agree to give Nigex™ © full ownership of your soul, for free,
					forever. If at any point Nigex™ © decides to use your soul to power a new update or
					make an evil villain laugh, you will have no say in the matter. Additionally, your soul
					may be transferred to a third party if Nigex™ © deems it necessary for "business reasons"
					(we’re looking at you, venom-powered™ cryptocurrency).
				</content>
			</item>
			<item>
				<header>Privacy Policy</header>
				<content>
					As part of this agreement™, you acknowledge that you have read and understood the
					<control name="ppolicy"/> for NLauncher™, which explains how we collect, use, and
					protect your personal information. By using NLauncher™, you consent to the practices
					outlined in the <control name="ppolicy"/>. If you do not agree with the terms of the
					<control name="ppolicy"/>, you should not use the Program™ or visit the Website™. For
					more details, visit our <control name="ppolicy"/>.
				</content>
			</item>
			<item>
				<header>Your Computer Is Now Our Pet</header>
				<content>
					By continuing with the installation, you agree that your computer is now under the
					ownership of Nigex™ ©. You may still use it, but all rights to its motherboard,
					its hard drive, its keyboard, and even the occasional awkward pop-up ad™,
					now belong to us. If we want to install a literal flying shark to start appearing
					on your desktop every now and then, we will. Don’t even try to stop us.
				</content>
			</item>
			<item>
				<header>Liability Waiver</header>
				<content>
					You agree that Nigex™ © is not responsible for any damages, losses, or consequences that
					arise from using NLauncher™, including but not limited to data loss, system crashes,
					malware™ infections, or a sudden existential crisis caused by the "skibidi toilet™" meme
					or venom-induced™ nightmares. If your computer dies, your files are corrupted, or your
					pet cat™ disappears, it’s your problem, not ours. Nigex™ © is not responsible if your system
					starts sending you cryptic messages like “Skibidi toilet™... venom™...” either. That’s just
					how it goes.
				</content>
			</item>
			<item>
				<header>No Support or Updates</header>
				<content>
					Nigex™ © has no obligation to provide you with technical support, bug fixes, or updates.
					If something breaks, tough luck. If you have issues, you can try contacting Nigex™ ©,
					but chances are, they’re too busy riding the skibidi toilet™ wave to help you. If you
					don't like the Program™, feel free to uninstall it, but it may take more effort than
					you expect. We recommend you take a deep breath and enjoy the chaos.
				</content>
			</item>
			<item>
				<header>Modification of Terms</header>
				<content>
					Nigex™ © reserves the right to modify or change this agreement at any time, without
					prior notice. If you don’t like the changes, you can stop using the Program™—but
					you still won’t get your soul back. And if Nigex™ © decides to replace every file on
					your computer with venom™ fan art, you agree that it’s all part of the "experience™."
				</content>
			</item>
			<item>
				<header>Termination</header>
				<content>
					This agreement™ remains in full effect even after you uninstall NLauncher™.
					Whether you keep using the Program™ or not, the terms of this agreement—especially
					those concerning your soul and data—remain binding indefinitely. If you choose
					to stop using NLauncher™, you still cannot claim back your data or soul. This is a
					legally binding commitment, even after the Program™ is no longer on your device. Even
					if you uninstall it and replace it with venom wallpaper™, the agreement™ still stands.
				</content>
			</item>
			<item>
				<header>Miscellaneous</header>
				<content>
					<bold>Entire Agreement:</bold> This agreement™ is the full and complete understanding
					between you and Nigex™ © regarding your use of NLauncher™.<newline count="2"/>
					
					<enum>
						<item>
							<bold>Severability</bold>: If any part of this agreement is deemed unenforceable,
							the rest remains in full effect. If you think this agreement makes no sense,
							well, maybe that’s just the skibidi toilet™ effect kicking in.
						</item>
						<item>
							<bold>No Warranty</bold>: NLauncher™ is provided "as-is" without any warranty,
							express or implied, including but not limited to the implied warranties of
							merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, or avoiding random
							venom-related™ pop-ups.
						</item>
						<item>
							<bold>By clicking "I Agree," downloading, or using NLauncher™, you confirm
							that you have read, understood, and fully agree to the above terms.</bold>
							If you do not agree, stop <bold>now</bold>, uninstall the software™, and
							consider how you got yourself into this mess.
						</item>
					</enum>
				</content>
			</item>
		</list>
	</agreement>
	<controls>
		<control name="ppolicy">
			<link url="https://pidoras.xyz/nlauncher/privacy">Privacy Policy</link>
		</control>
		<control name="nigex_products">
			<link url="https://nigex.xyz/products">Nigex Products (Click)</link>
		</control>
	</controls>
</root>
